<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Tours>
  <tour>
    <id>1</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>Playhouse Magical Cabaret</Title>
    <description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;Live cabaret, theater and ladyboy show twice a night at The Playhouse Magical Cabaret Theater at Suan Lum Night Bazaar. Featuring beautiful Thai dancers and stunning, stage designs that create scenes from around the world. It is a non-stop rollercoaster of entertainment that ranges through classical ballet, tap, hip-hop, contemporary styles, and famous pieces from international musicals Magical illusions and Spectacular voices and choreography will entertain visitors from around the world. The amazing BAZAAR Theater provides the finest state of the art presentations and have access to panoramic stage views. Staff will ensure you are comfortable with our unique Thai hospitality, our first performance is at 7:00 pm and the second at 8:30 Treat yourself and the entire family to a night out at one of the best evening attractions in Bangkok.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>2</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>OB Club - Virtual Golf  Party </Title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Experience the new way of playing golf simulator in the center of Bangkok. With the newest high technology GOLFZON VIRTUAL GOLF, you will enjoy incredibly realistic indoor golf environment offering the same golf feeling as you play in a real golf course, while other conditions are better. OB CLUB serves you more than 100 famous golf courses around the world (i.e. Pebble Beach, St. Andrews, Fuji, etc.).We commit to bring you into a new territory of golf.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>3</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>OB Club - Virtual Golf &amp; Party (18 holes)</Title>
    <description>Experience the new way of playing golf simulator in the center of Bangkok. With the newest high technology GOLFZON VIRTUAL GOLF, you will enjoy incredibly realistic indoor golf environment offering the same golf feeling as you play in a real golf course, while other conditions are better. OB CLUB serves you more than 100 famous golf courses around the world (i.e. Pebble Beach, St. Andrews, Fuji, etc.).We commit to bring you into a new territory of golf.</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>4</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title/>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The 1st Asian Show on Broadway, New York now arrived in Bangkok. Cookin&rsquo; NANTA Show is a comic non-verbal show for all ages. It is story about kitchen. The kitchen is thrown into a mess and cooks become wild as chefs chop, beat and stir in an attempt to meet the deadline. Kitchen knives &amp; many kitchen materials are transformed into musical instruments with chefs; they make unexpected amazing sound that will make you laugh with love. Cookin&rsquo; NANTA Show is the first Asian show to open its own theatre in Broadway, New York, USA and had Open Run for 3 years from Sep. 2003 to Sep. 2005. Over 10 million audiences from all over the world enjoyed the show. Finally Jan.2013 Cookin&rsquo; NANTA Show opens Bangkok theatre @ RCA, Played 1,000 times and over 100,000 people visited its Bangkok theatre.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>5</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title/>
    <description>The 1st Asian Show on Broadway, New York now arrived in Bangkok. Cookin’ NANTA Show is a comic non-verbal show for all ages. It is story about kitchen. The kitchen is thrown into a mess and cooks become wild as chefs chop, beat and stir in an attempt to meet the deadline. Kitchen knives & many kitchen materials are transformed into musical instruments with chefs; they make unexpected amazing sound that will make you laugh with love. Cookin’ NANTA Show is the first Asian show to open its own theatre in Broadway, New York, USA and had Open Run for 3 years from Sep. 2003 to Sep. 2005. Over 10 million audiences from all over the world enjoyed the show. Finally Jan.2013 Cookin’ NANTA Show opens Bangkok theatre @ RCA, Played 1,000 times and over 100,000 people visited its Bangkok theatre.</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>6</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>Art in Paradise Chiang Mai</Title>
    <description>&lt;p style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;Art in Paradise (Chiang Mai) the first Illusion Art Museum of Chiangmai, presents Illusion Art, the painting art requiring techniques and expertise in painting on a flat surface into a "3D" and giving a sense of realistic art. In addition, the museum also offers artworks in the form that allow visitors to take part in the artworks closely (Interactive Art), where the visitors can take photos with creative imagination, emotion and postures designed to correspond with each painting according to their own preferences as if they are a part of the painting. Therefore, Art in Paradise (Chiang Mai) is where the art is understandable for everyone, and happiness and entertainment are delivered to the visitor as well.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>7</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>Paint Bar Bangkok</Title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;??????????????? (Paint Bar Bangkok) ????????????????????????????????????????????????????? ???????????????????????????????????????? ???????????????????????????????????????????????????? ???????????????????????????????????????? ?????????????????? ??????????????????????????????????????? ???????????? ????? (Industrial Loft) ??????????????????? ??????????????????????????????????????????????? ???????????????????? ??????????????????? ???&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>8</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>ABC Morning Tour</Title>
    <description>&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Get out of your bed early at least for one day and get your lazy bones to work- to be precise physical work. And trust me, you&rsquo;ll love what you&rsquo;ll do, I guarantee! Head towards Khlong tan area (ABC Office) and find yourself among cyclists that are there for the same purpose as you: sightseeing the lively streets of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amujamu.com/en/locations/thailand/central-thailand/bangkok"&gt;&lt;span style="color:#2980b9"&gt;Bangkok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; by peddling on their cycles. As fun as it sounds, the experience will be so much more refreshing than you could have imagined.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;ABC Morning Tour(&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.amujamu.com/en/search/tours?q=abc&amp;date_range_start=&amp;date_range_end=&amp;category=&amp;location=&amp;creator_id=&amp;min_price=0&amp;max_price=0&amp;min_rating=&amp;page="&gt;&lt;span style="color:#2980b9"&gt;Amazing Bangkok Cyclist&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;) offers you with the opportunity to see and know the city in depth and at different hours. The locals, their morning rituals, how the street vendors set up their shops for breakfast and the morning view of the place, all combined shall be an adventurous morning all the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;When you are done crossing the Chao River with the help of our guide, on a long tail boat, you will be at the greener part of Bangkok even before you know. A beautiful and natural side of Bangkok awaits you there filled with green forests and its habitats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Explore the nature of Bangkok on your two wheels while you make a stop at the oasis for a break to cherish your surroundings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;p style="margin-left:0in; margin-right:0in; text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Highlights:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#13;
&#13;
&lt;ul&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Sightseeing the lively streets of Bangkok&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Freshly made foods from different vendors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
	&lt;li style="text-align:justify"&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:Tahoma,Geneva,sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span style="font-size:11pt"&gt;Amazing Chao Phraya River crossing on long tail boat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#13;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>9</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>ABC Afternoon Tour</Title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ABC afternoon tour will give you an insight in the lifes of the local people, walk over an old squeaky wooden bridge and explore communities build under the highway and next to the railway. This part of the tour will give you a very good impression about the daily rituals of the local people. After a drink stop we will cycle to the pier where we will cross the Chao Praya river with our longtail boat. Your bicycles will be carried out of the longtail boat for you. We arrived in the green heart of Bangkok.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
  <tour>
    <id>10</id>
    <CountryID>TH</CountryID>
    <Title>ABC Day Tour</Title>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ABC Biking day tour will give you a unique insight into the lifestyles of the local people in Bangkok. We will guide you through all layers of society, from high sky scrapers through Bangkok&rsquo;s biggest fresh market which is a jaw dropping experience. Here you will see vegetables you&rsquo;ve never seen before while lively chickens and fishes are jumping around. After a small tropical fruit break we will cycle through the small communities built up under the highway, where we will end up at the pier.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </tour>
</Tours>
